https://www.abilitycenter.com/ccpa-privacy-request/

Privacy Request Portal
We value the trust you put in us and understand that protecting your personal information is critical to earning and keeping that trust. Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), California residents are entitled to make certain requests regarding the personal information that Ability Center holds, shares, or uses about them. Please review Ability Center’s Privacy Policy for further information on what information we collect and why we collect it.
If you are a California resident and would like to submit a request under CCPA, please complete the form below. Following this submission, you will receive a verification email to confirm your request and must respond to the email in order for your request to be processed. Following this, we will ask you to verify your identity and respond to your request.
If you would like to know specific personal information collected about you within the past 12 months or know the categories of personal information collected about you, please select “Info Request” and include the details of your request in the box below.
In addition to the submission request, you may also submit requests at the following toll-free telephone number: 888.380.3765.
Please note: This portal is for Privacy related requests ONLY.
COVID-19 Your Safety is Important
Your safety and wellbeing are our top priority. With continued news around coronavirus (COVID-19), we want to share the steps we are taking to protect all customers and employees.
Read More
X
Request car price
CCPA Privacy Request
Name
Email
Phone
Request
